You know the analogy
I thought of if
you think about the
national security implications of
building models that
are essentially cognition that
are essentially intelligence right
I've called where we're
going with this a
country of geniuses and
a data center right
So imagine 100 million
people smarter than any
Nobel Prize winner and
it's going to be
under the of one
country or
So I think this
is I think it's
you it's a bit
like you I don't
know like selling you
know nuclear weapons to
North Korea and you
oh yeah Boeing made
the case your friend
David Sachs is basically
arming the No
I wouldn't refer to
any particular people but
I would just say
that this particular policy
think you Akin to
Yeah it's not well
advised